steinmart.com 2019-03-12

# Privacy and Security-Customer Service | Stein Mart

﻿

## Privacy Policy

Please note we have updated our privacy policy to more clearly describe our information collection and privacy practices. The new privacy policy will take effect on March 29, 2018 and can be found below. Your continued use of our site constitutes your agreement to our new privacy policy.

* * *

Safeguarding your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy describes our practices with respect to the collection, use and sharing of your personal information (also referred to herein as information). By publishing this Privacy Policy, we want you to know how your information will be collecte and used, and how it is protected. This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect in our stores or over the phone, as well as information we collect online. By using this site and shopping in our stores, you consent to the use of your personal information by Stein Mart and others in accordance with the terms of this Priavacy Policy and for the purposes described below.

Our published Terms of Use govern any dispute that may arise concerning our Privacy Policy or your use of our site, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, venue of disputes in Florida and application of Florida law.

In our Privacy Policy, you will learn:

  1. what types of personal information may be collected at this site
  2. how your personal information can be used
  3. who may have access to the information collected
  4. security procedures used to protect the information collected
  5. how to contact us to correct or cancel any information sent

### Types of information that we collect

We collect personal and other information from you at our stores, at this Site and via emails you may send us. The information we collect includes your name, address, email address, phone number, credit card and debit card information, date of birth and gender. You can also voluntarily provide information at our site through wish lists and product reviews that you submit. We may use cameras in and around our stores for security and operational purposes. We maintain standard web logs that record data about all visitors to this site. These logs may contain (1) the internet domain name from which you access the Site (e.g. ail.com, abc.org); (2) your IP address; (3) the type of browser and operating system you use; (4) the date and time you visited this site; (5) the pages you saw on this site; and (6) the address of the website you linked here from. Lastly we connect information, including current session information via "cookies" when you access our site.

As described below, we maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with applicable law to protect any non-public personal information we collect.

## How your Information is Used/Who has Access

We collect information from you in order to provide products and services that you purchase from us; register and service your online account; provide information that you request from us; contact you about your orders; process credit card and debit card transactions; ship products to you; send you promotional materials or advertisements about our products and services, as well as new features and offerings; administer surveys, sweepstakes, promotions and contests; and provide interest-based targeted advertising to you.

### Cookies and Direct Marketing

We use your information, information about you, and your browsing history to send you marketing e-mails and postal mail. We use our own cookies to help determine which of our ads are shown to you on our websites and other websites. Learn more about offsite advertising tracking and measurement and also learn [how to opt-out of these tools.](http://cmm.steinmart.com/TE_optout.html)

We also work with third-party companies that use their tracking technologies (including cookies and pixel tags) on our websites in order to provide tailored advertisements on our behalf and on behalf of other advertisers across the Internet. These companies may collect information about your activity on our sites and your interaction with our advertising and other communications and use this information to determine which ads you see on third-party websites and applications. Obtain more information about this practice and understand your options including how to [opt-out of receiving these tailored advertisements.](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/)

Please note that even if you opt-out, these tracking technologies may still collect data and you will still see ads, but they will not be targeted based upon the information collected through these tracking technologies.

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide certain features such as storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of the features on the site, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

* * *

### Affiliates/Joint Marketing

We share information among our subsidiaries and affiliates in accordance with our security standards and confidentiality policies, and applicable laws. We may also disclose your information to third parties that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other companies with whom we have joint marketing agreements.

### Business Partners and Agents:

We also may share information with non-affiliated business partners and agents with whom we have agreements to help perform functions on our behalf. Examples include filling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These parties have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

### Business Transfers

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. In the event that Stein Mart or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information, including information you have provided to Stein Mart, will be one of the transferred assets.

### Legal Protection of Stein Mart and Others

We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Stein Mart, our users, or others. This includes responding to subpoenas and other legal requests, exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. This does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitment set forth in this Privacy Policy.

### With Your Consent

In addition to the sharing described elsewhere in this Policy, we will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of Stein Mart when we have your consent to do so.

### Security of Information

We work to protect the security of your information during transmissions by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card processing company and credit card company during order processing. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when you have finished using a shared computer. You can access certain information we maintain about you by contacting us via email at [comments@steinmart.com](mailto:comments@steinmart.com). If you have register to use our Site, you can also access and update certain information by logging into your account and clicking on your email address and going to the My Account section of our Site. Please also see the Secure Shopping Guarantee section below.

### Privacy Policy Coverage

Please be aware that other sites and third-party content (for example, banner advertisements that you may access through our Site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those third party sites linked to our Site are not covered by this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is not intended to cover any information collection practices that take place outside of our site, regardless of whether they are controlled by us.

### Consent to Processing of Personal Data in the United States

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA) or other jurisdiction outside of the U.S., in order to provide our Site, products and services to you, we may send and store your personal information (also commonly referred to as personal data) outside of the EEA, including to the United States. Accordingly, your personal information may be transferred outside of the country where you reside or are located, including to countries that may not or do not provide the same level of protection for your personal information. We are committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of personal information when it is transferred. Where such transfers occur, we take appropriate steps to provide the same level of protection for the processing carried out in any such countries as within the EEA to the extent feasible under applicable law. By using and accessing our Site, users who reside or are located in countries outside of the United States agree and consent to the transfer to and processing of personal information on servers located outside of the country where they reside, and that the protection of such information may be different than required under the laws of their residence or location.

### Contact Us

If at any time you wish to contact us to correct or change any information that you have provided to us, if you have a question or complaint, or to exercise any of the rights set out in this Privacy Policy, including your opt-out rights, contact us by email at [comments@steinmart.com](mailto:comments@steinmart.com/) or use the contact information below:

> Stein Mart, Inc.  
>  Attention: Privacy Officer  
>  Address: 1200 Riverplace Boulevard, 5th Floor  
>  Jacksonville, FL 32207  
>  Telephone: (904)346-1500

You can also contact us through the Contact Us page of our website.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions of Use are also subject to change. Please check our Web Site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us via the contact information provided in the Contact Us section of this Policy.

## California Do Not Track Disclosure

* * *

Since Do Not Track technology has not been fully standardized, we do not respond to Web browser 'do not track' signals at this time. We await the result of work by the policy community and industry to determine when such a response is appropriate and what form it should take. We do allow you to exercise choice regarding the collection of information by third parties about your online activities over time and across third-party Web sites or online services for online interest based advertising purposes by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

The Network Advertising Initiative offers useful information about internet advertising companies, including information about how to [opt-outof interest-based advertising](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) by their members. You may also learn about online behavioral advertising and how to [opt-out from online behavioral ads](http://www.aboutads.info/consumers/) served by some or all participating companies.

These opt-out mechanisms rely on cookies to remember your choices with respect to ad-serving on websites. If you delete your cookies, use another computer or device, or change browsers, you will need to repeat this process. In addition, opting out of interest-based ads will not opt you out of all ads, but rather only those ads that are personalized to your interests based on activities observed on websites not owned and operated by Stein Mart.

## Secure Shopping Guarantee

* * *

We use the industry standard encryption protocol known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to keep your order information secure.

We have established a Secure Shopping Guarantee with Norton Security for every transaction that you make with Steinmart.com. Should any unauthorized charges appear on your credit card as a result of shopping with Steinmart.com, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.

_You should always see the Norton Shopping Guarantee seal with today's date displayed in the lower corner of the cart and checkout pages._

### The Norton Shopping Guarantee provides:

  1. $10,000 Identity Theft Protection - Receive comprehensive assistance and financial coverage if your identity is stolen anywhere online or offline.
  2. $1,000 Purchase Guarantee - All terms (returns, refunds, shipping, etc.) are independently guaranteed.
  3. $100 Lowest Price Guarantee - If the published store price drops, we will pay you the difference, up to $100.
  4. [Benefits, Terms and Conditions of the Norton Shopping Gaurantee](https://www.nortonshoppingguarantee.com/shoppers/terms-and-conditions/)
